Guys, you won't believe this!
- 방금 에이전트랑 얘길 했는데...
- 어머나!
-I just talked to my agent..
-Oh, my God!
I'm sorry. Too soon. You go.
미안, 너무 서둘렀네
말해봐
I got nominated for
Days of Our Lives!
생의 나날들로 후보에 올랐어!
-Good for you!
-Congratulations!
- 잘됐다!
- 축하해!
I can't believe you're nominated
for an Emmy!
네가 에미 시상식의
후보가 되다니!
-Soap Opera Digest Award?
-No. I'm up for a "Soapie."
- 소프 오페라 다이제스트 시상식?
- 아니, '소피'상 후보에 올랐어
Is that something you're making up?
그거 네가 만들어낸 거야?
No, no, no, it's real!
And it has been, since 1998.
아냐, 실존하는 거야!
1998년 이후로
레이첼!
나 '소피'상 후보에 올랐어!
I'm up for a Soapie!
Oh, my God!
어머나!
어머, 드라마 시상식 중에선
세 번째로 유명하잖아!
My God! That's the third most
prestigious soap opera award there is!
고마워! 다들 내가 누굴
시상식에 데려갈지 알겠지!
Thank you! I guess we know
who I'll take to the awards!
농담 아니지!
스타들 많이 오겠지?
Don't kid about that!
Will all the stars be there?
많이 오지
Many are scheduled to appear.
- 못 가겠어, 너무 떨려서!
- 내가 갈게
-I can't go. I'll be too nervous!
-I'll go.
넌 결혼하잖아
난 이것밖에 없어
You're getting married.
This is all I have.
The One With Joey's Award
Ernest Muhlbrat hypothesized that the
velociraptor, when threatened...
어니스트 멀브랫의 가설은
벨로시랩터가 위협을 느끼면
would expand its collar and
emit a high-pitched noise...
목을 부풀리고 고음의
소리를 내어서
to frighten off predators.
적을 쫓는다는 것이죠
Mr. Lewis?
루이스군?
What kind of noise?
어떤 소린데요?
Just a high-pitched,
intimidating noise.
고음의 위협적인 소리 있잖아
But like how?
어떻게요?
Well, we don't know for sure.
글쎄, 확실히 알 수는 없지
But in my head,
it sounded something like this:
내 생각엔
이런 소리였을 거야
Of course, this is just conjecture.
물론, 그냥 추측이야
Okay. That's all for today.
좋아, 오늘은 여기까지
Mr. Morse,
can I see you for a moment?
몰스군, 잠깐 볼까?
Yes, sir?
네, 교수님?
I need to talk to you
about your midterm exam.
중간고사 시험에 대해
얘기 좀 해야겠어
-I'm afraid I had to fail you.
-Why?
- F 학점 줘야 할 것 같아
- 왜요?
Well, you need 60% to pass.
패스하려면
60점은 돼야 하거든
- 난 몇 점인데요?
- 7점
-What did I get?
-Seven.
별로 안 좋군요
That's not so good.
아니, 안 좋지
네드, 무슨 일 있었니?
No, no, it's not.
What happened, Ned?
좀 봐주세요
전 사랑에 빠졌거든요
Maybe you can cut me some slack.
I'm sort of in love.
미안하지만, 그건
내 문제가 아니지
I'm sorry, but that's
really not my problem.
선생님과 사랑에 빠졌어요
I'm in love with you.
그건 조금 나랑 관련 있구나
That brings me in the loop a little.
그래서 시험 망친 거예요
집중이 안 됐어요
That's why I did so bad on this test.
I'm having a hard time concentrating.
교수님이 앞에서
수업하시는 모습이
When you're up there
and you're teaching...
아주 진지하셔서
and your face gets all serious...
멋져요, 교수님 그 딱 붙는
목 긴 스웨터 입을 때...
You look so good. When you wear that
tight little turtleneck sweater..
미안하지만
난 선생이야
I'm your teacher. I'm sorry.
넌 학생이구
You're a student.
그리고 난 여잘 좋아해
And I like women.
누가 뭐라고 의자 뒤에
낙서를 해 놨든 간에
In spite of what may be written
on the backs of these chairs.
저쪽 남자가
널 계속 주시하고 있어
That guy at the counter's
totally checking you out.
정말?
Really?
- 맙소사, 귀엽네!
- 가 봐
-Oh, my God, he's really cute!
-Go for it.
피비, 난 약혼했잖아
Phoebe, I'm engaged.
만약을 대비해서
전화번호 받아두라고
I'm saying, get his number,
just in case.
챈들러가 사고를 당해서
성불구가 된다거나 하면
But if Chandler's in an accident
and can't perform sexually...
네가 자신이 줄 수 없는 것을
다른 사람에게서 얻길 원할 걸
he'd want you to take a lover to
satisfy needs he'd no longer fulfill.
얘기할 게 있는데요
Can I just tell you something?
기쁘지만, 전 약혼했는데요
I'm very flattered, but I'm engaged.
This is kind of embarrassing.
좀 창피하네요
I actually came over
to talk to your friend.
실은 당신 친구랑
얘기하려고 온 건데
물론 창피하셔야죠
You should be embarrassed.
- 내가 그쪽 보는 건 줄 알았죠
- 알았지만 너무 재밌었어요
-I thought you knew I looked at you.
-I did, but that was really fun.
'수상자는...조이 트리비아니!'
"The winner is... Joey Tribbiani!"
'솔직히 기대 안 했어요'
"I honestly never expected this.
'수상소감 준비 못 했는데'
I didn't prepare a speech.
'항상 제 옆에 계셔주신
부모님께 감사 드리고요'
I'd like to thank my parents,
who've always been there for me.
'친구들에게도요, 챈들러
모니카, 피비, 레이첼...'
Also like to thank my friends,
Chandler, Monica, Phoebe, Rachel.."
- 난 네 번째야?
- 뭐야!
-I'm fourth?
-Jeez!
메이플 시럽 병이 상패야?
Look at you with your
maple syrup award!
다른 애들한테는
얘기 안 할거지?
Maybe you don't tell anyone
about this?
뭐 어때
난 샴푸 병 들고 그러는 걸
No big deal.
I do that with my shampoo bottle.
- 정말?
- 응
-Really?
-Yeah.
- 어떤 시상식 연습하는데?
- 그래미
-What award are you practicing for?
-Grammy.
For Best New Artist.
최고 신인상 부문
The Soapies people called today.
I also get to present an award.
소피 시상식 관계자가 전화했어
날더러 시상까지 하래
상 못 타도 무대에는 오르겠네
So you'll get on stage
even if you don't win.
- 내가 못 받을 거라고 생각해?
- 물론 아니지
-You don't think I'll win?
-Of course I do.
근데 최고의 컴백 인물?
그건 어렵잖아
But Favorite Returning Character?
That's a tough category.
화장됐다가 다시 살아 돌아온
배역하고 경쟁한다며
You're up against the guy who
survived his own cremation.
그래, 내가 못 탈 수도 있어
그치만 단지...
No, I know I might not win.
But it's just...
후보가 돼 본 적도 없었어
그래서 원하는 거야
I've never been nominated.
I want it so much.
분명히 탈 거야
You'll probably get it.
근데 '우아한 패자의 표정'도
연습해라
But you should start practicing
your "gracious-loser" face.
When the cameras are on you,
you want to look disappointed.
카메라가 널 비추면
실망한 모습을 보이면서도
But also that your colleague
deserved to win. Like:
동료가 수상할 자격이
있다는 듯이, 이렇게
You know?
알지?
-You practice losing the Grammys too?
-No, at the Grammys, I always win.
- 그래미 떨어지는 것도 연습해?
- 아니, 난 그래미는 항상 타지
-Hey!
-How'd your date go with Jake?
- 안녕!
- 데이트 어땠어?
Great. We couldn't keep
our eyes off each other.
좋았어, 서로에게서
눈을 뗄 수가 없었지
Every once in a while, he'd lean over,
stroke my hair, then touch my neck.
툭하면 기대어서, 내 머리를
쓰다듬고 목을 어루만졌지
그만해, 닭살이다
Stop it. You're getting me
all tingly.
계속 생각했던 건
'그가 키스할까' 뿐이었어
All I could think of was,
is he gonna kiss me?
- 했어?
- 난 숙녀야, 그런 말은 못 해
-Did he?
-I'm a lady. I don't kiss and tell.
근데 이 키스자국이
그걸 말해주지
But this hickey speaks for itself.
알았다, 알았어
Okay, I got it. I got it.
그 사람 너무 좋아
꼭 술 10잔은 마신 기분이야
I like him so much, I feel like
I've had 10 drinks today.
6잔밖에 안 마셨는데
I've only had six.
난 챈들러랑 처음 데이트 이후로
그런 느낌 못 느껴봤어
I haven't had that feeling since
I first went out with Chandler.
- 다시는 못 느껴볼 거야
- 꼭 남자같이 들린다
-I'll never have that feeling again.
-You sound like a guy.
아니, 남자는 '이젠 다른 사람이랑
잘 수 없을 거야' 하겠지
No, a guy would say, "I'll never
get to sleep with anyone else."
이젠 다른 사람이랑 못 자잖아!
I'll never sleep with anyone else!
결혼준비로 너무 바빠서
내가 뭘 포기하는 건지 잊었나 봐
I'm so busy planning the wedding,
I forgot about what I'll give up.
I'll never have a first kiss again.
다시는 첫키스란 없겠지
You'll have a last kiss.
마지막 키스는 있잖아
Can I ask you something? Has
a guy ever had a crush on you?
하나 물어봐도 돼?
남자가 너한테 반한 적 있니?
Is that why you wanted to tie my tie?
그래서 네가 타이를
매 준다고 한 거야?
내 학생 중 한 녀석이
날 사랑한대
A kid in my class said
he's in love with me.
와!
Whoa!
- 뭐가 '와'야?
- 로스가 남자친구 있대!
-Whoa, what?
-Ross has a boyfriend!
남자친구 없어
I do not have a boyfriend.
내 학생 중 한 녀석이
나한테 반했다는 거지
There's a guy in one of my classes
who has a crush on me.
- 정말?
- 그래
-Really?
-Yeah.
작년엔 엘리자베스
이번엔 이 녀석이고...
Last year, Elizabeth, now this kid...
뭐야? 내가 뭔가
그런 분위기가 있나?
What is it?
Am I giving out some kind of...
섹시 교수 분위기
sexy-professor vibe?
지금은 아닌데
Not right now.
요점은, 내 카리스마가 그 녀석
중간고사를 망치게 했다는 거야
The point is, my natural charisma has
made him fail his midterm.
그 녀석 불쌍하네
Now I feel bad for the kid.
나도 한 번 선생님
짝사랑했는데 너무 힘들었어
I had a crush on a teacher once,
and it was so hard.
집중이 안 됐어, 날 쳐다보시거나
하면 얼굴이 빨개지고
I couldn't concentrate.
I blushed every time he looked at me.
너도 그 나이 때
사랑에 빠진 기분 기억하잖아
You remember what it's like
to be 19 and in love.
- 좀 봐 줘야겠다
- 그래
-I can cut him some slack.
-Yeah.
- 넌 어떻게 극복했는데?
- 안 했어, 그냥 꼬셨지
-How'd you get over that teacher?
-I didn't. I got under him.
해결됐네
Problem solved.
- 안녕, 피비
- 알았어요, 잘 가요
-Bye, Phoebe.
-Okay, bye.
- 그래, 안녕
- 잘 가요
-All right. Bye.
-Bye.
닭살커플 티내지 않으려고
인사는 문 앞에서 다 했어
We said goodbye at the door
so as not to flaunt our new love.
괜찮아
내 앞에서 조심할 필요없어
It's okay.
You don't have to tiptoe around me.
생각해 봤는데 있지?
I've thought about it.
You know what?
괜찮아, 새로 사귈 때의
감정을 못 느껴도
I'm okay, not having that
new-relationship feeling.
- 벌써 보고 싶어!
- 나도 그래요!
-I miss you already!
-I miss you too!
멋지네, 하지만 내가
가진 것과 바꾸고 싶진 않아
That's great, but I wouldn't
trade what I have for that.
챈들러와 평생 같이
할 거니까, 그게 행복해
I'll be with Chandler the rest
of my life. That makes me happy.
여기 앉아 봐, 우리 관계가
얼마나 깊고 의미 있는지
Come sit down. We're talking
about how our relationship's deep...
얘기하고 있었어
자기도 그렇게 생각하지?
and meaningful.
It is, don't you think?
오, 그럼
Oh, totally.
내 손가락 당겨 봐
Pull my finger.
-Favorite Returning Male..
-This is my category!
- 컴백한 남자배우상...
- 내 부문이야!
- 소감 준비했어?
- 했어
-Got your speech?
-Got my speech.
우아한 패배자의 표정?
Got your gracious-loser face?
기억해, 상 타면
나 안아 줘야 돼
Try to remember, if you win,
you have to hug me.
엉덩이 잡아도 돼?
Can I squeeze your ass?
On TV?
TV에서?
그래!
Yeah!
남자 컴백 부문, 후보자들은
In the Favorite Returning Male
character category, the nominees are:
일반 병동의 존 윌러
John Wheeler from General Hospital.
끊임 없는 젊음의
개빈 그라함
Gavin Graham from
The Young and the Restless.
열정의
던킨 해링턴
Duncan Harrington from Passions.
그리고 생의 나날들의
조이 트리비아니
And Joey Tribbiani from
Days of Our Lives.
수상자는
And the Soapie goes to:
끊임 없는 젊음의
개빈 그라함
Gavin Graham from
The Young and the Restless.
뭐야...?!
Presenting the Favorite Supporting
Actress award:
여우조연상 시상은
생의 나날들의
조이 트리비아니가 하겠습니다
Joey Tribbiani from
Days of Our Lives.
Any one of the brilliant actresses
nominated for this award...
이 상의 후보에 오른
모든 여배우들은
deserves to take it home.
Unfortunately, only one can.
상 받을 자격이 있지만
불행히도 오직 한 명만 받겠죠
최우수 여자 조연상 후보는
The nominees for
Favorite Supporting Actress are:
열정의 에린 고프
From Passions, Erin Goff.
단 한번의 인생의 메리 로렌 비숍
내 아이들의 사라 르네
From One Life to Live, Mary Lauren
Bishop. All My Children, Sarah Renee.
생의 나날들의 제시카 애쉴리
And from Days of Our Lives,
Jessica Ashley.
수상자는
And the winner is:
생의 나날들의
제시카 애쉴리
Jessica Ashley from Days of Our Lives.
안타깝게도 제시카는
참석을 못 했습니다
Unfortunately, Jessica
couldn't be with us tonight...
그래서 제가 대신
수상 하겠습니다
so I'll accept this award
on her behalf.
분명히 제시카는
And I'm sure that Jessica...
저희 부모님께
감사할 거예요
wants to thank my parents...
항상 저를
믿어주셨거든요
who always believed in me.
제 친구들에게도
감사할 거예요
She'd also like to thank my friends:
챈들러, 모니카, 로스
피비와 바로 저기 앉아있는
Chandler, Monica, Ross,
Phoebe and Rachel...
레이첼
who's sitting right there.
왜 그렇게 급하게 왔어?
Why'd we rush out so fast?
이것 때문에 빨리 나와야 했어!
We had to get out of there
because.. Look what I won!
맙소사, 그 상 훔쳤구나!
Oh, my God. You stole her award!
아니, 그녀를 대신해서
받은 거지
No, no, no. I'm accepting it
on her behalf.
네가 대신이라는 뜻을
모르는 거 같다
I don't think you know
what "behalf" means.
알지, 동사잖아
'대신 가진다' 같은!
Sure I do. It's a verb.
As in "I be half-in' it"!
- 이거 되돌려 줘
- 내가 받았어야 했다구, 정말로
-You've got to take this back.
-I should've won. I really wanted it.
받으러 오지도 않았잖아
이것 그래미 상도 될 수 있어
She didn't care enough to come to the
thing. It could also be a Grammy.
안 돼, 조이
No, Joey.
아무도 못 봤어
잔뜩 쌓여 있었다구
No one saw me take it.
There's a whole table of them.
네가 타지도 않은
상을 갖고 싶어?
Do you want an award you didn't win?
아니, 내가 탄 상을 원해
그런데 아무도 안 주잖아!
No, I want an award I did win.
But nobody's given me any of those!
내가 이걸 진열해 놓으면
사람들이 와서 보고
If I put it up, when people come over,
they'll see it...
내가 탄 거라고
생각할 거 아냐
and think I won it.
조이, '최우수 여자 조연상'
이라 쓰여 있어
Joey, it says
"Best Supporting Actress."
긁어내면 되지
I can scratch that right off.
이건 잘못이야
갖다 줘
This is wrong.
You have to take it back.
이런 식으로 받는 건 안 돼
넌 능력 되잖아
You don't want to win an award
this way. You're very talented.
언젠가 정말로 탈 수 있을 거야
그리고 그게 너에게 소중한 거지
Someday you'll win one of these for
real and that one will mean something.
- 그래, 알았어
- 알았다구? 고마워
-Oh, all right.
-All right? Thank you.
- 내일 갖다 놓을게
- 그래
I'll take it back tomorrow.
내가 못 가지면
너도 가질 수 없어!
If I can't have it,
you can't have it!
- 겔러 교수님?
- 응, 루이스? 뭐 도와줄까?
-Professor Geller?
-Yes, Mr. Lewis? How can I help you?
중간고사
잘 못 본 건 아는데요
I know I didn't do well
on my midterms and stuff.
학점 변경을
해 주실 순 없는지요
But I was hoping you could
change my grade.
내가 왜 그래야 하지?
And why, exactly, would I do that?
교수님을 사랑하니까요
Because I'm in love with you.
뭐?
What?
정말 사랑하고 뭐 그렇거든요
Yeah. I'm all in love
with you and stuff.
-So could you change my grade?
-No!
- 바꿔 주실 거죠?
- 안 돼!
Why not? You changed Ned's grade.
왜 안 돼요?
네드는 바꿔 주셨잖아요
That's different. Because he was
actually in love with me.
그건 다르지
걔는 진짜로 날 좋아했거든
No, he's not!
He's totally yanking your chain.
아니에요!
교수님을 속인 거라구요
He's done this with
three other teachers.
교수님 말고도
다른 세 분이나 당했다구요
-What?
-He's got a girlfriend.
- 뭐야?
- 걔 여자친구 있어요
I can't believe someone
would do that for a grade.
어떻게 성적 때문에
그럴 수가 있지
I know.
그러게요
It's awful.
너무하죠
I love you.
난 교수님 사랑해요
-Have you seen Chandler?
-No, why?
- 챈들러 봤어?
- 아니, 왜?
I keep thinking about all
the things I won't have.
내가 앞으로 가질 수 없는 게
뭔지 생각해 봤거든
It's freaking me out.
I don't know what to do.
화가 나서 참을 수 없어
어쩔 줄을 모르겠고
Don't sweat it.
간단해
Chandler's not around, so get it
out of your system. That guy's cute.
챈들러 없을 때 해버려
쟤 귀엽다
Come on, I'm serious.
난 심각해
-I've got to talk to him about this.
-That's the last thing you want to do.
- 챈들러하고 얘기를 좀 해야겠다
- 그건 절대 하면 안 되는 얘기지
-Why?
-Because you're marrying him!
- 왜?
- 걔랑 결혼할 거니까
You gotta help me out here.
뭔 소리야
I've never been engaged.
I've never really been married.
난 약혼도 안 해봤고
결혼도 진짜론 안 해봤으니
I can only tell you
what my mother told me.
우리 엄마가 내게
해 준 얘기 해 줄게
When you have doubts or fears or
anxieties about a relationship...
남녀 관계에 의심이나 겁이나
또 근심이 생기기 시작하면
don't communicate them
to your husband.
남편과는 그런 얘기 하지 말라고
I'm not supposed to share
my doubts and fears...
평생을 같이 할 사람과
with the guy I'm spending
the rest of my life with?
그런 의심들을
나누면 안 된다고?
That is correct. Yes.
맞아, 그래
You're supposed to put all that stuff
in a little box in your mind...
그런 건 마음의
한편에 놔 두고
and lock it up.
얘기하지 마, 참으라구
- 네 엄마가 그래?
- 응
Your mother told you this?
The woman who married a bunch of times
and killed herself when you were 13?
결혼 몇 번씩 하다가
너 13살 때 자살한 엄마?
Oh, my God, you're right.
진짜로 그렇네
Tell Chandler.
Hurry, before it's too late!
더 늦기 전에
챈들러한테 말해!
Wait! Does this also mean that
putting out doesn't get you love?
잠깐! 그럼 헤프게 굴어야
사랑받는단 말도 틀린 건가?
'실버컵'
-I'm gonna meet Jessica Ashley!
-Wait, wait.
- 제시카 애쉴리를 만나다니!
- 잠깐, 잠깐
Rach, please be cool, okay?
I work with this woman.
레이첼, 좀 진정해
난 그 여자랑 동료잖아
그래, 진정됐어
Okay, I'm totally cool.
들어오세요
Come in.
- 안녕하세요, 제시카
- 안녕하세요
Hey, Jessica.
Hey, Jess.
This is my friend Rachel.
제 친구 레이첼이에요
-Hi.
-What's up?
- 안녕하세요
- 별일 없죠?
Here's your Soapie.
I accepted it for you.
소피상 여기 있습니다
제가 대신 받았어요
Oh, my God. I won?
Do you have any idea what this means?
제가 수상했다고요?
이게 어떤 의미인지 알아요?
You're not gonna put it
on your shelf or anything?
장 위에다 진열 안 하세요?
No, I try to save that for real
awards. Now if you'll excuse me?
진짜 상을 위해서 아껴 둬야죠
잠시 실례
-Take it back?
-Absolutely.
- 다시 가져갈까?
- 그럼
Yeah, you do!
그래, 잘 한다!
Honey?
As we get closer to the wedding...
자기야?
결혼이 가까워질 수록
is there anything
you'd like to share?
뭔가 같이
나누고 싶은 것 없어?
Okay. I think the centerpieces
are too big.
꽃장식이 너무 큰 것 같아
You're wrong.
The centerpieces are fine.
아냐, 꽃장식은 좋아
-Do you ever get scared at all?
-Kind of. They're really big.
- 자긴 겁 안 나?
- 조금, 너무 크단 말야
Doesn't it freak you out that you'll
never be with anybody new again?
다시는 새로운 사람과
만날 수 없다는 게 겁 안 나?
What?
뭐?
I love you so much.
자길 너무 사랑해
Sometimes it bothers me that
I'll never have that feeling.
그런 감정이 더는 없을까봐
겁날 때가 있어
When you first meet someone...
사람 처음 만나면
and it's new and exciting.
You know that rush?
새롭고 흥미롭잖아
그런 기분 알지?
No, when I first meet somebody...
아니, 난 사람을 처음 만나면
it's mostly panic, anxiety
and a great deal of sweating.
긴장되고 초조하고
식은 땀이 나
Okay. But you're a guy.
근데 자긴 남자잖아
Aren't you freaked out that you'll
never sleep with anybody else?
다른 사람과 못 자게
된다는 게 겁나지 않아?
Sleeping with somebody, no.
누구와 같이 자는 것, 별로인데
Anxiety, panic and, I'm afraid,
even more sweating.
긴장되고 초조하고 식은 땀이
더 많이 나지
Even with me?
나랑도?
I was dangerously dehydrated the
first six months of our relationship.
처음 6개월 동안
너무너무 힘들었어
For me, the rush is knowing that we'll
be together the rest of our lives.
내게 새롭고 흥미로운 건 우리가
평생 함께 할 거란 사실이야
-Really?
-Well, yeah.
- 정말?
- 그래
Knowing you're having these thoughts,
we're back to panic, anxiety and...
네가 이런 생각을 하는 걸
알고 나니 또 초조하고 긴장되고
I'll definitely need
some kind of sports drink.
이온음료 좀 마셔야겠어
Come here. Oh, you don't
have to worry.
이리 와
걱정할 필요없어
Besides, you know what? I'll have
a lot of new things with you.
또, 자기랑 새로운 일도
많이 할 건데 뭐
The first time we buy a house. Our
first kid. Our first grandkid.
처음 집 살 때, 첫 애 가질 때
첫 손주 볼 때
Water. Water. Water.
물, 물, 물
Mr. Morse? Can I speak to you
for a moment?
몰스군? 잠깐 얘기 좀 할까?
That was a great lecture today.
Did you get a little haircut?
멋진 강의였어요
머리 자르셨어요?
Yeah, yeah. Do you like it?
Do you love it?
그래, 괜찮니?
사랑하니?
I want you to know I'm
changing your grade back.
네 성적 원상복귀 했단다
What? Why?
뭐라구요? 왜요?
I know what you're trying
to pull here. It won't work.
네가 무슨 속셈인지 알아
그렇게는 안 되지
I'm not trying to pull anything.
Look, I love you, dude.
아무 속셈 없어요
사랑해요, 교수님
I'm not even gonna talk about this.
This little "thing" is over.
말할 것도 없다
이 사건은 끝났어
I know you have a girlfriend.
And I know about the other professors.
여자친구 있는 거 알아
다른 교수들 일도
How do you think that makes me feel?
You used me!
내 기분이 어떨 거 같아?
넌 날 이용했어!
You don't love me and you never did!
넌 날 사랑하지 않아!
한 적도 없구!
Professor Winston.
Professor Frederickson.
윈스턴 교수님
프레드릭슨 교수님
I'll be right with you.
곧 가지요
Don't make this worse and I'll
give you a "C." Shall we?
더 상황 악화시키지 않으면
C학점 줄게, 가실까요?
금방 나갈게
I'll be out in a second.
"It's just so unexpected!
'전혀 기대 못했어요!'
I'll tell you, it's such
an honor to just be nominated...
'후보에 오른 것만도
영광이죠'
for a Nobel Prize.
'노벨상이라니'
And, you know, to win one
for a massage!
'게다가 마사지 부문에서
수상 하다니!'
Especially just after winning a
Tony Award for Best Actress.."
'게다가 토니 여우주연상을
받은 직후이고...'
Our reservations are at 8.
우리 8시 예약이야
"in Reservations at Eight
by Neil Simon.
'닐 사이몬의 8시 예약으로
수상했죠'
Thank you, Neil.
Thank you for the words."
'닐, 고마워요
좋은 가사를 써 줘서'
Finish this later.
We're gonna be late.
나중에 해, 늦겠다
Please don't play the music.
Just one more thing.
분위기 깨지 말아 봐
한 마디만 더
Okay. "Live from New York,
it's Saturday Night!"
'뉴욕에서 라이브로
토요일밤입니다!'